[Music]
first off I'd like to offer you all a
warm welcome from here in Melbourne
where the sun shine seld you might be
anywhere at all in this world be boys
and be girls we're bringing and pearls
and like you we're unique in the
Treasure we speak and this music we make
cultivates our belief so let me kick an
introduction on the drum and yet
Beginnings begun and roll call the
components my name is jistic I'm CC p on
the scratch and your rock wor
the that we are teed you how do you do
do what you do c you love to do what you
do we do we I te Ed you how do you do do
you do what you do cause you love to do
what you do we
do
we started off on Street sides with hand
drums upgraded to this where the
grandsons of diggers and widows
immigrants Engineers gamblers Jazz
collectors and fishermen all PE that
root to panoramic looser than pan
jamming from Sid to mels New Plymouth to
Pakistan you could be on the bus they
dreaming out the window a walking the
bush track it don't matter what you're
into we've been shopping beats talking
about what we've been through now we
done the mic check let the show
continues cuz these four fellas are
Terren mcken a storytellers telling our
tales and leaving trails like an Trails
tipping the scales until the cloud C the
clears and these weird ideas move minds
and Rears from earliest Beginnings to
these current proceedings from trees
down to seedlings we age well like rling
so while we're breathing people keep
reading Sue's mission statement is to
keep on keeping for the cats with no
cash or the folks in the Mansions we
formed a band for the thinkers and
dancers the ones curious looking for
answers the instrumental
rocking the jamming the gold
medalists all the swimming and damn kids
the Old Settlers all the tribes whose
landed is the Rockers and the B Star the
fruit vendors and the art Bohemians the
whole D demographic this band stops
trafficing back street to padic we put
the down for the addicts and the fiends
and the friends who feel the soul of the
music how
do what you do you love to do what you
do we do we are teas at you how do you
do do you do what you do CA you love to
do what you do we
[Music]
do d d d
we all right here it goes here it goes
come in
[Music]
come who's
that